Akian
阿基安
i have everything
我已拥有一切
If you want
如果你想
I am here
我在这里
this hand
这只手
Can I hold on?
我能坚持住吗？
Big lady ‥
大小姐‥
Go quickly and meet Huawei Wei.
快去见华为魏。
He lost a lot of blood.
他失了很多血。
Please speak carefully. What happened to Hua Rongzhou?
请仔细说话。华荣洲怎么了？
Hurry up and meet me, madam.
女士，快点来见我吧。
Teacher, thank you so much for today.
老师，今天非常感谢您。
Come see us off and leave your books.
来送我们吧，留下你的书。
I just pretended I didn't hear anything else.
我只是假装没有听到其他声音。
I don't think I need to mention it again in the future.
我想以后不需要再提了。
walk
走
House owner
房子的主人
you talk about me
你谈论我
I've been waiting for this for so long
我等这个很久了
Why are you so anxious now?
你现在怎么这么着急？
like a little boy
像个小男孩
Doctor, how is Huarongzhou?
医生，华容洲怎么样了？
Go back to your wife, people at home are fine.
回到你老婆身边吧，家里人都很好。
It's just that the wound broke down a second time.
只是伤口第二次破裂了。
Thank you for your hard work
感谢你的努力工作
I'm taking medicine now
我现在正在吃药
I'm already asleep
我已经睡了
Second crack?
第二次裂痕？
- Qian Zhi - Yes, honey.
- 钱志 - 是的，亲爱的。
what's the matter?
怎么了？
Don't you know, madam?
夫人你不知道吗？
Back to the girl's story, guard Hua was injured as the sun was setting over the cliffs.
回到女孩的故事，花警卫在夕阳西下的时候受伤了。
Maybe it was because I got slapped by my uncle again yesterday.
也许是因为昨天我又被叔叔打了耳光。
Only then did the wound open again
直到这时伤口才再次裂开
Fall off a cliff?
从悬崖上掉下来？
That Lihua escort followed that girl.
那个梨花侍卫跟着那个女孩。
fall into a valley together
一起跌入山谷
He did not return with her until the next morning.
直到第二天早上他才和她一起回来。
We saw a wound on his back
我们看到他背上有伤口
Probably when I fell
大概是我摔倒的时候
I accidentally got scratched by a tree branch.
我不小心被树枝划伤了。
He didn't say much to us either.
他也没有对我们说太多。
Would you like to follow me down the valley?
你愿意跟我一起下山谷吗？
Muyao, you owe me
慕瑶，你欠我的
-Lady - Aquian‥
-女士- 阿奎安‥
Why didn't you tell me?
你为什么不告诉我？
He was injured?
他受伤了？
Madam, these days, because
女士，这些天，因为
Feeling depressed and silent all day
整天心情低落、沉默寡言
I can't hear a word anyone else says.
我听不到别人说的一句话。
After all, it's just a nursing home.
毕竟，这只是一个疗养院。
He didn't even listen to his own advice
他连自己的劝告都不听
How dare we say anything at this point?
这个时候我们还敢说什么？
Guard Hua insisted on guarding the courtyard despite being wounded.
华警卫带伤坚持守卫院落。
Yesterday I got slapped by my uncle again.
昨天我又被叔叔打了。
The person was like this without saying a word.
那人就这样，一言不发。
Until he couldn't take it anymore and passed out in front of me.
直到他再也无法忍受，昏倒在我面前。
Only then did I realize how badly he was hurt.
直到那时我才意识到他伤得有多严重。
- But the eldest lady doesn't care at all - Cuizhu
——可是大小姐根本不在乎 ——翠竹
-Fahrenheit protects him‥ -Woman
-华氏度保护他‥ - 女人
The doctor just prescribed some medication and told me to take it later.
医生只是开了一些药，让我稍后再吃。
Let's go down and take a look first.
我们先下去看看吧。
I told you before that I like ignoring you.
我之前就说过我喜欢无视你。
I'm not sure yet
我不肯定
Now it seems
现在看来
You all care deeply about me.
你们都很关心我。
But I'm always selfish and only think about myself
但我总是自私，只考虑自己
This applies to you
这适用于你
Same goes for my brother.
我的兄弟也是如此。
decent
体面的
It's not too late this time, I found it
这次还不算太晚，我找到了
What kind of dream was this?
这是一个什么样的梦呢？
I hold on too tightly and won't let go
我抓得太紧不肯放开
Do you wake up and your wound still hurts?
你醒来后伤口还疼吗？
Can you let go now?
现在可以放手了吗？
What I said just now isn't over
我刚才的话还没有结束
I was dragged here because of you
我是因为你才被拖到这里来的
This subordinate deserves to die.
这个属下该死。
Please punish my master.
请惩罚我的主人。
What crimes deserve death?
哪些罪行该死？
You are seriously injured.
你受了重伤。
It's a good idea to go back to bed and get some rest.
回到床上休息一下是个好主意。
wake up quickly
快点醒来
You put the clothes on first.
你先把衣服穿上。
See you later
回头见
I didn't sleep well last night
我昨晚没睡好
I want to squint a little more.
我想再眯一会儿。
If anything happens, call me back.
如果有什么事，请给我回电话。
Last night I was guarding the yard gate
昨晚我守着院门
Honey, are you in the Chinese escort room?
亲爱的，你在中国伴游室吗？
He is sleepy and I can't wake him up.
他很困，我无法叫醒他。
stayed a little longer
停留的时间长一点
Don't worry, lady. Luckily, I thought about it last night.
别担心，女士。幸好我昨晚就想到了。
It seems the girl has gone back to bed.
看来女孩已经回床上去了。
Other people fooled me like this
别人就是这样愚弄我的
What do I care about?
我关心什么？
Differences Between Men and Women
男性和女性之间的差异
Besides, he is still master and servant.
更何况，他还是主仆。
Girl, you better be more careful
姑娘，你最好小心点
If this spreads widely
如果这件事广泛传播
I am afraid of losing my identity.
我害怕失去我的身份。
I know what people say is scary
我知道人们说的话很可怕
But because of me, Huarongzhou was seriously injured.
但因为我，华容洲受了重伤。
Even if you serve tea and water in his room
即使你在他的房间里端茶和水
Also appropriate
也合适
if it were you
如果是你的话
I'll be the same too
我也会一样
Now for me
现在对我来说
For a long time you were no longer servants.
很长一段时间以来，你们不再是仆人了。
So please don't say things like that from now on.
所以从现在开始请不要说这样的话。
Probably around this time
大概这个时候
in this place
在这个地方
None of this is appropriate
这些都不合适
But I still want to ask if you are willing.
但我还是想问你愿不愿意。
If you have my other half in your heart
如果你心里有我的另一半
Leave everything else to me
其他的一切都交给我
I will make you fair and good
我会让你变得公平和善良
stand next to me
站在我旁边
Akian
阿基安
i have everything
我已拥有一切
If you want
如果你想
I am here
我在这里
The girl just went to bed. What do you want?
女孩刚去睡觉，你想做什么？
If it's not urgent, let's talk later.
如果不紧急的话，我们晚点再说吧。
kneel down and punish
下跪惩罚
There's no need to give the girl an alarm
没必要给女孩敲警钟
Why are you kneeling here?
你为什么跪在这里？
The medicine is ready
药已备好
- What are you going to do? - Please get out of the way. I have a favor to ask you, Madam.
- 你会怎样做？ - 请让开。女士，我有件事想拜托你。
No, she's still sleeping
不，她还在睡觉
-You can't go in. -Please get out of the way.
-你不能进去。 -请让开。
- Tsuiju ‥ You cannot enter - Madam ‥
- 翠树 ‥ 不能进入 - 女士 ‥
- I have a question, ma'am. - You can't go in, Kuiju.
- 我有一个问题，女士 - 你不能进去，Kuiju。
－Big Lady ‥ －Qian Ji ‥
－大小姐‥ －千姬‥
What's going on outside?
外面发生了什么事？
- I have a question to ask - Cuizhu, I told you.
- 我有个问题要问 - 翠竹，我告诉过你了。
-You let go . -You really can’t go in, she’s still sleeping.
-你放手 。-你真的不能进去，她还在睡觉。
oldest woman
最年长的女人
Yesterday, Guard Hua was seriously injured and lost consciousness.
昨天，华警卫受了重伤，失去了知觉。
okay…
好的…
For loyalty to protect the Lord,
为了忠诚地保护主，
Just don't punish the person.
只是不要惩罚这个人。
When did I punish him?
我什么时候惩罚过他了？
Guard Hua is now kneeling outside.
华护卫现在跪在外面。
Qianzhi, help me comb my hair.
千芝，帮我梳一下头发。
Cuizhu, please bring Hua Rongzhou later.
翠竹，稍后请带花容舟来。
yes
是的
There's no need to kneel
没有必要跪下
The injury didn't heal
伤势并未痊愈
Why don't you just lie down?
你为什么不直接躺下呢？
-Who punished you? -Her subordinate got angry with the girl.
-谁惩罚了你？ - 下属对女孩很生气。
deserve to be punished
应该受到惩罚
Why are you so honest?
你为什么这么诚实？
I told you I was nothing
我告诉过你我什么都不是
i was thinking
我刚在想
Take a break and ask again
休息一下再问
I think it would be better to forget about it now.
我认为现在最好忘记它。
Please save me the trouble of thinking alone.
请免除我独自思考的麻烦。
Please go down first. I have something to ask that person.
请先下去吧，我有话要问那人。
i ask you
我问你
You found me so quickly that day in the valley
那天你在山谷里这么快就找到了我
Did you jump with me?
你和我一起跳了吗？
yes
是的
What about back injuries?
背部受伤怎么办？
Did you get scratched when you fell?
你摔倒的时候有没有被抓伤？
no
不
After my men landed on the river,
当我的人在河上登陆后
Traces of a man dressed in black were found.
发现了一名黑衣男子的痕迹。
I thought about it
我想过这个问题
That's the man in black who jumped with him.
那就是和他一起跳下去的黑衣人。
I'll attack first
我先进攻
I was injured while fighting him.
我和他打斗时受伤了。
etc.
ETC。
If the fight continues
如果战斗继续
I am afraid that it will become more difficult to find the person you are looking for.
恐怕要找到你要找的人会变得更加困难。
Have you seen his face?
你见过他的脸吗？
he covered his face
他捂住脸
maybe i misunderstood
也许我误解了
This man in black doesn't want to fight me at all
这个黑衣人根本不想和我战斗
So after both sides suffered losses,
所以在双方都遭受损失后，
he left in a hurry
他匆匆离开
I couldn't catch up either.
我也追不上。
I'm sorry I don't think you misunderstood.
抱歉，我不认为你误会了。
Jumped off a cliff and got hurt
从悬崖上跳下受伤
Why don't you tell me these things?
你为什么不告诉我这些事情？
Because the girl didn't ask
因为女孩没有问
I've been so depressed these days
我这几天心情很郁闷
But what will happen to you next?
但你接下来会发生什么？
You should take the initiative and tell me.
你应该主动告诉我。
Did you understand?
你明白了吗？
I am always busy with my work.
我的工作总是很忙。
Too many aspects cannot be covered
太多方面无法涵盖
I know you usually talk less
我知道你平时说话比较少
But you've done so much for me
但你为我做了这么多
I need to learn how to speak positively to myself.
我需要学习如何积极地对自己说话。
I have never seen you as a servant
我从来没见过你是仆人
So, you can talk freely.
所以，你们可以自由地交谈。
I don't think you're trying to show off.
我不认为你是想炫耀。
i know
我知道
Also, if you are injured, you need to take good care of yourself.
另外，如果你受伤了，你需要照顾好自己。
Don’t force yourself to accept Zhong Yeran’s cheek when he tries to cause trouble.
不要强迫自己接受钟野然的脸皮，当他试图制造麻烦时。
Before protecting others
在保护他人之前
First you need to learn how to protect yourself
首先你需要学会如何保护自己
Did you understand?
你明白了吗？
That girl once said this to me.
那个女孩曾经对我说过这样的话。
But I've thought about it privately for a long time.
但我私下里思考了很长时间。
To me, a woman...
对于我来说，一个女人...
Our people are so nice
我们的人民真好
I don't care what happens to me
我不在乎我会发生什么
I just don't want to see that girl suffer any injustice.
我只是不想看到那个女孩受到任何不公正的对待。
all right
好的
You quickly go back and lie down.
你赶紧回去躺下。
Guarding the yard is not necessary these days.
现在已经没有必要看守院子了。
good luck
祝你好运
If you need anything, please contact Qian Zhi.
如果您有什么需要，请联系钱志。
yes
是的
correct
正确的
I have poor eyesight.
我视力不好。
From now on, I should wear less black clothes.
从现在开始，我应该少穿黑色衣服。
Otherwise I wouldn't have even known you were hurt.
不然我根本不会知道你受伤了。
good
好的
Will you choose or not?
你会选择还是不选择？
If you don't choose one of the two
如果您不选择两者之一
I don't want either.
我也不想要。
This way you don't have to worry.
这样你就不用担心了。
Feeling guilty for only saving one person
只为救一个人而感到内疚
Muyao, you owe me
慕瑶，你欠我的
-Lady - Aquian‥
-女士- 阿奎安‥
Are you okay?
你还好吗？
uncle
叔叔
Middle selection up and down
上下中间选择
Go immediately and do your best to find the whereabouts of the big lady.
立即前往，尽全力寻找大小姐的下落。
yes
是的
walk
走
Yesterday I went to Huashen's funeral.
昨天我去参加了华神的葬礼。
News of breakup with Hua Qian
与华倩分手的消息
I have to spread it today
今天我必须传播它
Why suddenly?
为什么突然？
suddenly?
突然？
Are you having a hard time waiting even a few days these days?
这些天你是不是连几天的等待都很难受？
I don't know what my uncle is talking about.
我不知道叔叔在说什么。
correct
正确的
Hua Qian told me to bring the message.
华谦叫我带口信来。
what?
什么？
She said you owe her
她说你欠她的
two lives
两条生命
Ouch
哎哟
Earlier you said that I blindly trust Hua Qian.
刚才你说我盲目相信华潜。
She took advantage of this to commit numerous tricks.
她利用这个机会，做了很多的事。
great
伟大的
she used to
她曾经
What about you?
你呢？
parking
停車處
-document -here it is
-文档 -就是这里
let's go
我们走吧
What's in the bag?
包里面有什么？
It's all clothes
都是衣服
walk
走
Please check carefully
请仔细检查
- Let's go, hold on. - Thank you.
- 我们走吧，等一下 - 谢谢
next
下一个
Stop and check it out
停下来检查一下
- Stop. - Did you see that?
- 停下来 - 你看到了吗？
I've never seen it before...
我以前从未见过...
-Wait a minute, have you seen anyone suspicious? -no
-等一下，你有看到可疑的人吗？ -不
Why are there so many officers and soldiers on the streets?
街上为何有这么多官兵？
owner
所有者
Martial law is now becoming more stringent in this city.
这个城市的戒严现在变得更加严格。
People leaving the city, people behaving badly on the streets.
人们离开城市，人们在街上行为恶劣。
Individual D-Shop customers are being questioned one by one.
个别D-Shop顾客正在接受一一询问。
Although the owner changes restaurants every few days,
虽然老板每隔几天就会更换餐厅，
But as time goes by
但随着时间的流逝
It's inevitable that someone will notice
难免有人会注意到
Have you found a way out of the city?
你找到离开城市的路了吗？
The main entrance is strictly prohibited
主入口严禁进入
There is strict security and interrogation.
有严格的安全和审讯。
The eastern side of the city has Donghuang Mountain in the background.
城东侧背靠东黄山。
The road over there is rough and steep.
那边的路又崎岖又陡。
A place no one would normally pass by
通常没有人经过的地方
So the guards were so weak that they came and went.
于是侍卫兵力薄弱，便来来去去。
we can give it a try
我们可以尝试一下
escape?
逃脱？
No, there aren't many of us in the city now.
不，现在城里我们的人不多了。
If the owner wants to leave
如果主人想离开
Then other people will create chaos at the front door
然后其他人就会在前门制造混乱
lead the people
领导人民
Then leave unnoticed on the east side of the city.
然后悄悄地离开城市的东侧。
It's not difficult
这并不难
owner
所有者
The longer you delay, the harder it will be to leave.
拖得越久，就越难离开。
What am I drawing?
我在画什么？
at last
终于
I lost my wife and I lost my army.
我失去了我的妻子，我失去了我的军队。
But that's my parrot
但这是我的鹦鹉
That person should have been mine too
那个人也应该是我的
It was definitely love at first sight
这绝对是一见钟情
I just found something that suits me
我刚刚找到了适合我的东西
excuse for temptation
诱惑的借口
I should have known sooner
我应该早点知道
Grab the person and run away
抓住人就跑
owner
所有者
are you okay
你还好吗
Just do what you say.
照你说的去做。
this car
这辆车
Your brother sent me here before.
你哥哥之前派我来这里的。
He knows I like cars.
他知道我喜欢汽车。
I spent a lot of gold and silver
我花了很多金银
I went and bought this fragrant tea.
我去买了这香茶。
I scolded him often.
我经常骂他。
But he still didn't listen
但他还是不听
and me
和我
I can't bear to let others taste it either.
我也不忍心让别人尝到。
Give it a try and see what happens
尝试一下，看看会发生什么
How is your mother these days?
你妈妈最近怎么样？
Don't cry or make a fuss
不要哭泣或大惊小怪
much more stable
更稳定
If it's okay, go to that person's room and see them often.
如果可以的话，就去那个人的房间，经常看看他们。
After all, you are now her only child.
毕竟你现在是她唯一的孩子了。
She won't bother you when she wakes up.
她醒来后不会打扰你。
What's the problem?
有什么问题？
decent
体面的
It must be a legacy of a previous injury.
它一定是以前受伤的遗留物。
Try living a little
试着生活一点
I will give you your brother's memorial tablet.
我会把你哥哥的牌位给你。
return to hometown shrine
回到故乡神社
At that time, I will resign from my position as governor.
届时，我将辞去州长职务。
To avoid the clan's old stubbornness
为了避免家族的旧顽固
I see that I have lost my will
我发现我已经失去了意志
It is inevitable that other thoughts will arise that interfere with it.
不可避免地会出现其他干扰它的想法。
Everything is according to the will of the Father
一切都按照天父的旨意
Qian Er
千儿
Is there a place in particular that Qian’er wants to go?
千儿有什么特别想去的地方吗？
What about after this problem is over?
这个问题解决之后呢？
Let’s not rush and go back to our hometown.
我们先别着急，赶紧回家乡去吧。
Take a little trip around
四处旅行一下
By the way, please take care of your mom and rest in peace.
顺便说一句，请照顾好你的妈妈，安息吧。
Think of it this way
这样想
After spending many years in Hwangcheong
在黄清度过多年之后
I never took you out alone
我从来没有带你一个人出去
It's actually because I've neglected you too much.
其实是因为我太忽视你了。
Dad, can you help me?
爸爸，你能帮我吗？
Did you run into a problem?
您遇到问题了吗？
My security guard was hurt.
我的保安受伤了。
I want to check something
我想检查一下
But there is no one around who can use it.
但周围却没有人可以使用它。
tell me something
告诉我一些事
I'll help you solve it
我帮你解决
It's no big deal
没什么大不了的
I can do it myself
我能自己做
Qian Er
千儿
You can call the people in this house whatever you want.
你可以随意称呼这所房子里的人。
you don't have to tell me
你不必告诉我
When there is a special problem that cannot be resolved
当遇到特殊问题无法解决时
Please say again
请再说一遍
thank you father
谢谢你父亲
Why are you being more polite to me?
为什么你对我客气多了？
Drink it quickly
快点喝掉
Second daughter...
二女儿...
People have already chosen
人们已经选择了
these guys are pretty good
这些人都很好
After all, people are smart
毕竟人都是聪明的
There are too few people
人太少了
I'll pick a few more later.
稍后我会再选几个。
good
好的
You don't need to show him again.
你不需要再给他看。
Then you just follow what I say.
那你就照我说的去做吧。
Just organize it.
整理一下吧。
But according to the second girl's command,
但按照二姑娘的吩咐，
you six
你们六个
I will go and guard the area around Zhongyi in a moment.
我一会儿就去镇守忠义一带。
There are two main points:
主要有两点：
one
一
Special attention needs to be paid to
需要特别注意的是
Mu Xiaoniang’s every move
穆小娘的一举一动
When she leaves, you follow.
当她离开时，你也跟着走。
don't warn the snake
不要警告蛇
Tell me who she met when she came back
告诉我她回来后遇见了谁
Second, I want to check if anyone visits the servant's house at night.
第二，我想查一下晚上有没有人去仆人家。
Then find out the whereabouts of this person.
然后打听这个人的下落。
Just come back and report it
回来报告一下就可以了
Yes, the second girl.
是的，第二个女孩。
I don't care if I get found
我不在乎是否被发现
Just tell me you are Hwa-sai's guard.
就告诉我你是华西的守卫吧。
Follow my orders and monitor Mu Yao from here.
听从我的命令，在这里监视慕瑶。
No matter what other people say
不管别人怎么说
subordinates know
下属知道
go down
下去
yes
是的
second girl
第二个女孩
Even if those people are good at it
即使那些人很擅长
I'm worried that I won't be able to fully monitor Zhongzhai.
我担心自己无法全面监控中寨。
After all, there are many capable people in Zhongzhai.
毕竟中寨的能人不少。
i know
我知道
So I just left it alone.
所以我就不管它了。
Just look at Muyao
看看慕瑶就知道了
You will find 6 more people later.
稍后你会发现另外6个人。
Please take turns working with 6 people right now.
现在请 6 个人轮流工作。
Remember, don't relax at all
记住，一点都不要放松
Hwangcheong is currently under martial law.
黄清目前处于戒严状态。
There's no escape for a while
一时之间无处可逃
Moreover, depending on the personality
另外，还得看个人性格
It's impossible to just leave without saying goodbye.
不辞而别是不可能的。
So, you have to keep an eye on Mu Yao.
所以，你必须盯紧慕瑶。
not a last resort
不是最后的手段
don't fight her
别和她打架
I don't want to deal with Mu Yao yet.
我还不想和慕瑶打交道。
playing the piano to a cow
给牛弹钢琴
Second daughter, don't worry
二女儿，别担心
I will definitely tell them again and again.
我一定会一次又一次地告诉他们。
just do your best
尽力而为
After all, if a monk can escape, he cannot escape from the temple.
毕竟，修士能逃，就逃不出寺庙。
yes
是的
time doesn't wait
时间不等人
I can't do this and I can't wait any longer.
我不能这样做，我不能再等了。
You go to the servant's garden and hand him a congratulatory card.
你去仆人的花园，递给他一张祝贺卡。
Just tell the eldest princess I will thank her tomorrow.
你就告诉大公主我明天一定会感谢她的。
yes
是的
bank
银行
You always take good care of my jewelry.
你总是照顾好我的珠宝。
Once upon a time when the big princess married me,
曾几何时，大公主嫁给我的时候，
Do you still remember the white jade bracelet I gave you?
你还记得我送你的白玉手镯吗？
slaves remember
奴隶记得
Then help me find it.
那你帮我找找吧。
I am going to the bell garden tomorrow
明天我要去钟花园
Some things must be returned
有些东西必须归还
Yes, it's a girl
是的，这是一个女孩
uncle
叔叔
I just came back from outside
我刚从外面回来
I discovered secret people around me
我发现了我周围的秘密人
I secretly observed
我偷偷观察
They seemed to be looking at Zhong Zhai.
他们似乎在看着钟宅。
Whose person is this?
这是谁的人？
It seem to be like that
好像是这样的
fahrenheit family people
华氏家庭成员
Change your clothes and go do something
换件衣服去做点事
yes
是的
Princess, the big girl is here
公主，大姑娘来了
I met a big princess
我遇见了一位大公主
come and sit
过来坐
yes
是的
Don't meet for a few days.
几天不见面。
You look much slimmer
你看起来瘦了很多
I haven't been able to leave the house these days.
这几天我都不敢出门。
Where is the weight loss?
减肥去哪儿了？
big princess
大公主
In fact, this time, apart from saying thank you,
其实这一次除了说声谢谢之外，
I have come to return this bracelet to you.
我是来把这只手镯还给你的。
In the end I let you down
最后我让你失望了
What I have given you is yours.
我给你的就是你的。
You don't have to come back to me again
你不必再回到我身边
This was passed down by the late emperor to his eldest daughter.
这是先帝传给他长女的。
As an outsider, I cannot and should not dare to accept him.
作为一个外人，我不能也不应该接受他。
What does it mean to be an outsider but not an outsider?
做外人而不是外人是什么意思？
Even if there is no fate with Laner
就算和兰儿没有缘分
You don't have to see me outside
你不必在外面看到我
Just think of it as a reward from your senior.
就当是前辈给你的奖励吧。
Thank you so much, princess.
非常感谢你，公主。
since you got married
自从你结婚以来
I watch all your performances
我看你所有的表演
You are a wise child who knows how to advance and retreat.
你是一个聪明的孩子，懂得进退。
Lander doesn't have much luck.
兰德的运气并不好。
I just got here
我刚到这里
I'm not that stupid girl
我不是那个傻女孩
I only know how to show grace to my children.
我只知道如何对我的孩子们表现出恩典。
From now on you can't go away from me
从今以后你就不能再离开我了
If you want to come to the Bell Garden
如果你想去贝尔花园
just come and meet me
来见我吧
save me from loneliness
救我脱离孤独
Are your parents okay?
你的父母还好吗？
a few days ago
几天之前
That bogey family is so arrogant
那个忌家人太嚣张了
public assassination
公开暗杀
Don't take our Zhong family seriously at all.
根本不把我们钟家当回事。
We were the ones who got your brother in trouble after all.
毕竟是我们给你兄弟带来了麻烦。
Chief these days
酋长这几天
In pursuit of this problem, I had trouble sleeping and eating.
为了追寻这个问题，我寝食难安。
I seem to have lost a lot of weight
我好像瘦了很多
It's my brother's fate
这是我兄弟的命运
meet a sister like me
遇到一个像我这样的姐妹
speaking
请讲
I almost missed it two days ago
前两天我差点错过了
I made the decision for you and forgot to leave.
我替你做了决定，却忘了离开。
Then I thought about it
然后我想了想
I heard the head of the household gave orders.
我听到一家之主发号施令。
Princess, thank you for thinking of me.
公主，谢谢你还想着我。
I can't wait any longer
我不能再等了
So I sent someone to deliver the letter to the Central Committee.
于是我就派人把这封信送到了中央。
The head of the household just remembered and gave the command.
户主这才想起来，下达了命令。
Chief these days
酋长这几天
to track down the assassin
追查凶手
I'm so busy that I can't even come to the backyard often.
我太忙了，连后院都不能经常来。
I don't get to see him often either.
我也不常见到他。
I remembered it the other day and sent someone to bring food.
那天我想起来了，就派人送饭来了。
The result was all in vain
结果一切都是徒劳
He was always a steady person.
他一直是一个稳重的人。
I don't know why
我不知道为什么
I don't know if you know me
我不知道你是否认识我
Then he quietly slipped out of the servant's garden.
然后悄悄溜出仆人花园。
If it had been the day before yesterday, the head of the household would have gone to see me.
如果是前天的话，一家之主就来看我了。
Our family sympathizes with you on the recent loss of your brother.
我们的家人对你最近失去兄弟表示同情。
I miss my dad again
我又想念我的爸爸了
Despite years of service to the Zhong family,
尽管为钟氏家族服务多年，
See for yourself
你自己看
He sent me a certificate of reconciliation.
他给我寄了一份和解证书。
What happened to the owner this time?
楼主这次怎么了？
so inappropriate
太不合适了
Don't take it to heart
别放在心上
From now on, I will never again allow that person to disturb your peace.
从今以后，我再也不会允许那个人打扰你的平静了。
big princess
大公主
Wait until the truth about Mr. Jong's garden party assassination is revealed.
等到有关Jong先生游园会被刺杀的真相揭晓。
The father will resign himself and return home
父亲将辞职回家
Then I'll go with that person.
那我就跟那个人一起去吧。
I am afraid that I will never return to the Imperial City again in this life.
这辈子恐怕再也回不了皇城了。
why?
为什么？
This Hwangcheong is where my brother grew up.
这黄清是我哥哥长大的地方。
It doesn't matter to me
这对我来说并不重要
Or to your parents
或者给你的父母
It's not easy to stay for long.
想要长久停留并不容易。
great
伟大的
This can be happen
这可能会发生
don't blame me
别怪我
The family has always cherished faces.
一家人一向很珍惜面子。
Siu and Raynor have been siblings since childhood.
Siu 和 Raynor 自幼就是兄妹。
If there is a scandal between brothers
如果兄弟之间有绯闻
I'm afraid I won't be able to protect you either.
我恐怕也保护不了你。
Thanks for reminding me, princess.
谢谢你的提醒，公主。
Mom, I want to play too
妈妈我也想玩
Wait a minute , mom, can I put it up a bit more?
等一下 ，妈妈，我可以再多放一点吗？
I want to let myself go
我想放飞自我
Would you like to solve it yourself?
您想自己解决吗？
Wait for me to raise it and raise it a little higher
等我举高一点
I want to let myself go
我想放飞自我
then you chase me
然后你追我
Mom, I'll do it myself.
妈妈，我自己来吧。
mother, please give it to me
妈妈，请给我
myself
我
I'll let you go myself
我会亲自放你走
come
来
If you like it, hold on tight
如果喜欢就紧紧抓住
great?
伟大的？
Come on, play with me
来吧，和我一起玩吧
If you like it, hold on tight
如果喜欢就紧紧抓住
What are you dreaming about?
你在梦什么？
I hold on too tightly and won't let go
我抓得太紧不肯放开
continued
继续
Thanks for watching
感谢您的观看